Finding Aid for the Edwin S. Shneidman Papers LSC.0385
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Suicide Research
  - Patient letters and notes [name withheld] (1 of 2) -- Restricted., 1976. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Patient letters and notes [name withheld] (2 of 2) -- Restricted., 1976. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Patient notes and letters [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1979-1980. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - "Clark, Dick" notes -- Restricted., 1970. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous notes and correspondence on suicide notes and reflections -- Restricted., 1970s. (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Pabbas -- Restricted., undated. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - July 1983 Suicide notes -- Restricted. (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - August 1983 Suicide notes -- Restricted., 1983 August. (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - September 1983 Suicide notes -- Restricted., 1983 September. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Suicide notes, October 1983 -- Restricted., 1983 October. (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - November 1983 suicide notes -- Restricted., 1983 November. (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - December 1983 Suicide notes -- Restricted., 1983 December. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - May 1984 Suicide notes -- Restricted., 1984 May. (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - June 1984 Suicide notes -- Restricted., 1984 June. (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Terman Study Project -- Restricted., 1981. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Terman study materials -- Restricted., 1981 June 9. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Terman Study, Andrus Foundation grant notes -- Restricted., 1986-1987. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Terman Study, forms and approaches -- Restricted., 1989. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Terman Study, forms -- Restricted., undated. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Terman Study, miscellaneous (1 of 2) -- Restricted., 1970- c. 1984. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Terman Study, miscellaneous (2 of 2) -- Restricted., 1970- c. 1984. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Terman Study Cases, notes -- Restricted., 1980s. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Terman Study suicide case [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1980s. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Terman Study correspondence and death certificates -- Restricted., 1981. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Terman Study notes -- Restricted., 1980s. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Terman Study suicide notes -- Restricted., 1970s-1980s. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Suicide notes -- Restricted., 1983. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Terman Study case file -- Restricted., 1976 May 11. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Suicide notes, rosters -- Restricted., 1983-1984. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Suicide notes, miscellaneous -- Restricted., 1987 November 3. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Suicide notes, typed draft -- Restricted., undated. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Notes -- Restricted., 1983 July, August. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Suicide notes, draft -- Restricted., 1984, 1987. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - January 1984 suicide notes -- Restricted., 1984 January. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - March 1984 suicide notes -- Restricted., 1984 March. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Patient profile (2 of 5): TAT [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1986 October. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - April 1984 suicide notes -- Restricted., 1984 April. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Patient profile (3 of 5): MAPS Test Record of a Neurotic Subject [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1987. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - February 1984 suicide notes -- Restricted., 1984 February. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Patient profile (4 of 5): MAPS -- Restricted., 1987. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Patient profile (1 of 5): letters, notes [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1986. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Patient profile (5 of 5): MAPS -- Restricted., 1987. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Patient MAPS test [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1962 March 20. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - MAPS (materials) -- Restricted., 1986. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence with Leenaars on suicide notes -- Restricted., 1986. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Leenaars - ESS Study (1 of 3) -- Restricted., 1986. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Leenaars - ESS Study (2 of 3) -- Restricted., 1985-1986. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Leenaars - ESS Study (3 of 3) -- Restricted., 1985-1986. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Peterson Death -- Restricted., 1987. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Includes two audio cassettes.
  - Uncategorized notes -- Restricted., 1980s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Consent form "A Multi-Disciplinary Psychiatric Taxonomy," blank -- Restricted., 1980 April. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - BSRG Support (Terman Study) -- Restricted., 1981 and 1989. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Patient profile and notes [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1994. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Twin Study - Restricted., undated. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sprague, interviews -- Restricted., undated. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Letters from suicidal people -- Restricted., 1955-1999. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "An Interim Concordance Study of Terman Gifted Septogenarians" proposal, correspondence -- Restricted., 1985 December 23. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Copy of Johannes Junius 1628 letter to daughter upon his death -- Restricted., undated. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - The Suicidal Mind, diaries [names withheld] -- Restricted., 1979. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Murray's manifest needs -- Restricted., undated. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Consent Form, "Terman Study of the Gifted (UCLA Sub-Study)," blank -- Restricted., 1981 July 1. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Psychological Pain Assessment Survey (PPAS), filled out [names withheld] (1 of 2) -- Restricted., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Psychological Pain Assessment Survey (PPAS), filled out [names withheld] (2 of 2) -- Restricted., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Psychological Pain Assessment Survey (PPAS), filled out [names withheld] (1 of 4) -- Restricted., 1994. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Psychological Pain Assessment Survey (PPAS), filled out [names withheld] (2 of 4) -- Restricted., 1994. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Psychological Pain Assessment Survey (PPAS), filled out [names withheld] (3 of 4) -- Restricted., 1994. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Psychological Pain Assessment Survey (PPAS), filled out [names withheld] (4 of 4) -- Restricted., 1994. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - PPAS HAM - ESS -- Restricted., 1998. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Psychological Pain Assessment Scale I & II, patient files (1 of 2) -- Restricted., 1998. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Psychological Pain Assessment Scale I & II, patient files (2 of 2) -- Restricted., 1998. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - PPAS -- Restricted., 1999 and 2005. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - UCLA (blank forms, lists) -- Restricted., 1999 November 16. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Thematic Apperception Test (TAT) -- Restricted., 1998-1999. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Interview with patient, transcript -- Restricted., 1983. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Autopsy of a Suicidal Mind correspondence, patient files, and notes [names withheld] -- Restricted., 2002-2003. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Terman Study Subjects, Key [names withheld] -- Restricted., 1993. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Unfiled suicide notes and letters [names withheld] -- Restricted., 1980s. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous suicide notes, photocopies [names withheld] -- Restricted., undated. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous research materials, letters, and notes [names withheld] -- Restricted., c. 1970 - c. 1990. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous research materials, letters, and notes [names withheld] -- Restricted., c. 1970 - 1980s. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Rorschach Test -- Restricted., c. 1940s. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Kammerman and the 93 NYPD Officers [names withheld] -- Restricted., 1985-1987. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Suicide data, NYPD ca. 1930-1940 [names withheld] -- (1 of 4) Restricted., undated. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Suicide data, NYPD ca. 1930-1940 [names withheld] -- (2 of 4) Restricted., undated. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Suicide data, NYPD ca. 1930-1940 [names withheld] -- (3 of 4) Restricted., undated. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Suicide data, NYPD ca. 1930-1940 [names withheld] -- (4 of 4) Restricted., undated. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Psychological Autopsy of "S" [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1983. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Golden Gate Bridge barrier (1 of 4), correspondence, notes, and suicide notes -- Restricted., 1960s. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Golden Gate Bridge barrier (2 of 4), prevention activities, including plan for barrier -- Restricted., 1960s - 1970s. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Golden Gate Bridge barrier (3 of 4), suicide clippings -- Restricted., 1960s - 1970s. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Golden Gate Bridge barrier (4 of 4), correspondence -- Restricted., 1977. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Uncategorized notes -- Restricted., undated. (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Accession [insert accession number] backlog material (Box 38A, Box 38B, Box 38C, Box 39, Box 40A, Box 40B, Box 41, Box 42A, Box 42B)